INNA ARABEJO

Plano, TX, 75024

214-682-3521 | Email: inna.arabejo@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/inna-arabejo-449699171/
Portfolio: https://inna-arabejo.github.io/creative-portfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/inna-arabejo

A web developer that is versed in building projects from the ground up. Utilizing extensive background in customer service to provide seamless, attentive, and user-friendly experiences for end-users. An up-and-coming graduate of the Full Stack Web Development program from SMU Continuing and Professional Education; a rigorous program with a primary focus on MERN Stack web applications. When faced with a challenge, I put forth a willingness to learn, adaptability, and a commitment to the belief that as a team; together everyone achieves more.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-end: Javascript, React, HTML, CSS

Back-end: MySQL, Git, MongoDB, Node.js, Express **Technologies**: GitHub, VS Code, Git, Bootstrap, NPM

PROJECTS

junkfood.

Deployed Page: https://inna-arabejo.github.io/g3p-junkfood/
Repository: https://github.com/inna-arabejo/g3p-junkfood/

- **Summary:** To create a dynamic front-end web application that incorporates an immersive UI experience. Implemented 2 or more third-party APIs, the web application provides and displays still and animated content suitable for ages 13 and up.
- **Role:** 1 of 3 contributors. Worked on Splash and Login pages, "goodies" page, local storage allocation, and custom CSS and bootstrap design.
- Tools: JavaScript, Bootstrap v4.6, HTML, CSS, APIs, local storage functionality.

Note Taker

Deployed Page: https://note-taker-inna.herokuapp.com/
Repository: https://github.com/inna-arabejo/note-taker

- **Summary:** An application that allows a user to organize their thoughts and keep track of tasks that need to be completed. Utilized Express.js which will save and retrieve note data from a JSON file.
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: JavaScript, NPM packages, Node.js, Express.js

Daily Planner

Deployed Page: https://inna-arabejo.github.io/daily-work-planner/ **Repository:** https://github.com/inna-arabejo/daily-work-planner

- **Summary:** A planner that allows you to save events from 9am 5pm. This planner enables an employee with a busy schedule to add important events so that they can manage their time effectively. Applied the Moment.js library to work with date and time.
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap v4.6, Moment.js

EXPERIENCE

SMU CAPE — Student Developer

February 2022 - May 2022

Dallas, TX

A web developer program centered on preparing professionals for high-growth careers in the digital economy. Currently gaining in-demand skills and implementing complex logical conditions to meet an objective and initiate projects from idea to execution.

Key Accomplishments:

- Integrated agile methodologies to simulate a professional work environment and complete tasks in a timely-manner over a 1-week deadline.
- Logged over 500+ hours of learned-material inside and outside of the classroom while successfully completing 12 projects.

Beauty & Essex — Hostess

August 2020 - December 2020

Los Angeles, CA

Delivered knowledge of customer-service principles and processes to provide guests with high-class hospitality in a fast-paced restaurant. Coordinated with coworkers and managers accordingly to achieve operational excellence.

Key Accomplishments:

- Demonstrated understanding of tasks and began training new hostesses after one month of getting hired.
- Resolved guest inquiries and communicated to manager and team members.

AlphaBest Inc. — Zone Leader

August 2018 - March 2019

Frisco, TX

Administered an after-school program with co-workers. Nurtured an interactive, fun, and positive learning environment for children from Kindergarten to 5th grade.

Key Accomplishments:

- Promoted effective communication with team members to set a structured schedule and curriculum for successful operational flow.
- Led lessons that stimulated creative growth through arts and craft activities.

EDUCATION

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development – SMU

February 2022 - May 2022

Certificate, AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner – AWS Digital Training

January 2022

Associate of Science, General Studies – Collin College

August 2017 - May 2020